A Finding Aid to the Fendrick Gallery Records, 1952-2001, in the Archives of American Art AAA.fendgall
Archives of American Art
- Museums and Galleries Files, 1952-2000, undated; Series 5; (Box 64-72, OV 114; 9.25 linear feet)
  - Domestic Museums and Galleries, 1952-2000, undated; 5.1
    - Louisiana (Box 67)
      - Alexandria Museum Visual Arts Center, Alexandria, La., 1983-1985, undated (Box 67)
      - New Orleans, Miscellaneous, 1974-1977, 1981-1986, undated (Box 67)
    - Maine (Box 67)
      - Art Spaces, Inc., Portland Museum of Art, Portland Maine, 1974, 1994-1995. undated (Box 67)
      - Bowdoin College Museum of Art, Brunswick, Maine, 1975-1977, 1983-1989 (Box 67)
    - Maryland (Box 67)
      - Baltimore Museum of Art, Baltimore, Md., 1974-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 67)
      - Judy Evans, Potomac, Md., 1988 (Box 67)
      - Maryland Arts Council, Baltimore, Md., 1974-1983, undated (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous, 1970 (See also OV 114), 1977-1992, undated (Box 67)
      - Tusculum Farm (Carl Freeman), Gaithersburg, Md., 1984-1990, undated; (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - Massachusetts (Box 68)
      - Springfield Museum of Fine Arts, Springfield, Mass., 1976-1977 (Box 68)
      - University of Massachusetts, Amherst, Mass., 1973, undated (Box 68)
      - Vesti Corporation, Boston, Mass., 1983, 1987, 1992, undated (Box 68)
      - Williams College Museum of Art, Williamstown, Mass., 1973-1974, 1985, undated (Box 68)
    - Michigan, Miscellaneous (See also OV 114), 1973-1993, undated (Box 68)
    - Minnesota (Box 68)
      - Bird Island Publishing, Inc., Minneapolis, Minn., 1979-1981, undated (Box 68)
      - Hansen-Cowles Gallery, Minneapolis, Minn., undated (Box 68)
      - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, Walker Art Center, Minneapolis, Minn., 1975-1976, 1990-1991, undated (Box 68)
      - Minnesota Museum of Art, St. Paul, Minn., 1980, 1985 (Box 68)
    - Mississippi, Mississippi Art Association, Jackson, Miss., 1969 (Box 68)
    - Missouri (Box 68)
      - Albrecht Art Museum, St. Joseph, Mo., 1975-1976 (Box 68)
      - Greenberg Gallery, St. Louis, Mo., 1974, 1984, 1987 (Box 68)
      - Hellmuth, Obata, and Kassabaum, St. Louis, Mo., 1984, undated (Box 68)
      - St. Louis/Clayton, Mo., Miscellaneous, 1965-1991, undated (Box 68)
    - Nebraska (Box 68)
      - Joslyn Art Museum, Omaha, Nebr., 1977-1978, 1984 (Box 68)
      - University of Nebraska Art Galleries, Lincoln, Nebr., 1975-1985, undated (Box 68)
    - Nevada, Stremmel Gallery, Reno, Nev., undated (Box 68)
    - New Hampshire (Box 68)
      - The Currier Gallery of Art, Manchester, N.H., 1974-1976 (Box 68)
      - Hood Museum of Art/Hopkins Center Art Gallery, Dartmouth College, Hanover, N.H., 1973-1976, 1984, undated (Box 68)
    - New Jersey (Box 68)
      - The Art Museum, Princeton University, Princeton, N.J., 1974-1985, undated (Box 68)
      - Miscellaneous, 1973, 1976-1979, 1984-1985, undated (Box 68)
      - The Newark Museum of Art, Newark, N.J., 1974-1975, 1984-1985 (Box 68)
    - New Mexico (Box 68)
      - Morning Star Gallery, Santa Fe, N. Mex., 1984, undated (Box 68)
      - Roswell Museum and Art Center, Roswell, N. Mex., 1975-1976 (Box 68)
    - New York (Box 68)
      - Abbeville Press, New York, N.Y., 1985 (Box 68)
      - Alexander Milliken Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1983-1986 (Box 68)
      - Albany, N.Y. Miscellaneous, 1974 (Box 68)
      - Albright-Knox Art Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1972-1986; (2 folders) (Box 68)
      - American Craft Museum, New York, N.Y., 1982-1986, 1990, undated (Box 68)
      - Andre Emmerich Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1972-1989, undated; (4 folders) (Box 68)
      - Arnot Art Museum, Elmira, N.Y., 1975 (Box 68)
      - Brooke Alexander, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1979-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 68)
      - Brooklyn Museum, Brooklyn, N.Y., 1976-1985, 1996, undated (Box 69)
      - Coe Kerr Contemporary, New York, N.Y., 1983 (Box 69)
      - Colgate University, Hamilton, N.Y., 1971-1976, 1984, undated (Box 69)
      - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y./Ithaca College, Ithaca, N.Y., 1969-1984, undated (Box 69)
      - Edward Lenkin, New York, N.Y., 1986 (Box 69)
      - Everson Museum of Art, Syracuse, N.Y., 1971-1973, 1984, undated (Box 69)
      - Figura, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1988 (Box 69)
      - Fischbach Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1975-1988, undated (Box 69)
      - Forum Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1981-1983, 1988 (Box 69)
      - Fraunces Tavern Museum, New York, N.Y., 1979 (Box 69)
      - Frumkin Gallery, New York. N.Y., 1976-1988, 1993, undated (Box 69)
      - Gettler/Pall, New York, N.Y., 1977-1983 (Box 69)
      - Gimpel and Weitzenhoffer, New York, N.Y., 1978, 1984, undated (Box 69)
      - Grace Borgenicht Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1952, 1970, 1973-1983, undated (Box 69)
      - Guggenheim Museum, New York, N.Y., 1985 (Box 69)
      - G. W. Einstein Company, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1972-1980, undated (Box 69)
      - Harry N. Abrams, Inc./Abrams Original Editions, New York, N.Y., 1977-1982, 1985, undated (Box 69)
      - Iolas-Jackson Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1982-1983 (Box 69)
      - Jay Spectre, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1988 (Box 69)
      - Katherine Markel Fine Arts, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1979-1981, 1985-1986, undated (Box 69)
      - Kennedy Galleries, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1962-1964, 1971-1974, 1988, undated (Box 69)
      - Leo Castelli Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1980-1985, undated (Box 69)
      - Marlborough Gallery, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1967-1973, 1978, 1982-1985, undated (Box 69)
      - Max Protetch, New York, N.Y., 1985, undated (Box 69)
      - Memorial Gallery of the University of Rochester, Rochester, N.Y., 1970-1985, 1988, undated (Box 69)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art, New York, N.Y., 1976-1981 (Box 69)
      - M. Knoedler and Co., New York, N.Y., 1974-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 69)
      - Monique Knowlton Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1977-1978, undated (Box 69)
      - Multiples, Inc./Marian Goodman Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1979-1981, undated (Box 69)
      - Munson-Williams-Proctor Institute, Utica, N.Y., 1968-1972, 1985, n.d (Box 69)
      - Museum of Contemporary Crafts, New York, N.Y., 1977 (Box 69)
      - The Museum of Modern Art, New York, N.Y., 1975-1988, 1991-1992, undated (Box 69)
      - Nancy Hoffman Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1978-1985, undated (Box 69)
      - The New Museum, New York, N.Y., 1979-1980 (Box 69)
      - New York City, Miscellaneous, 1968-1991, undated (Box 69)
      - Nina Freudenheim Gallery, Buffalo, N.Y., 1979-1982 (Box 70)
      - Pace Editions, Inc./The Pace Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1971-1982, 1990, undated (Box 70)
      - Parasol Press, Ltd., New York, N.Y., 1971-1990, undated (Box 70)
      - Patricia Heesy Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1987 (Box 70)
      - Paula Cooper, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1988-1989 (Box 70)
      - Petersburg Press, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1986, undated (Box 70)
      - Robert Miller Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1982-1987, undated (Box 70)
      - Robert Schoelkopf Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1979-1987 (Box 70)
      - Rochester, N.Y. Miscellaneous, 1970-1982, 1991, undated (Box 70)
      - Rock Spring Studio, Ithaca, N.Y., 1989, 1991, undated (Box 70)
      - The Schenectady Museum, Schenectady, N.Y., 1976-1977 (Box 70)
      - Scottsville, N.Y., 1985 (Box 70)
      - Sherry French Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1984-1985 (Box 70)
      - Sidney Janis Gallery, New York, N.Y., 1970-1973, 1984 (Box 70)
      - Sotheby Parke Bennett, New York, N.Y., 1973-1992, undated (Box 70)
      - State University College, Fredonia, N.Y./Webb and Parsons, Bedford Village, N.Y., 1976-1977 (Box 70)
      - Steven Miles Kossak, New York, N.Y., 1976-1983, undated (Box 70)
      - Tribal Arts, New York, N.Y., 1973, undated (Box 70)
      - Vassar College Art Gallery, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1975-1977, 1985 (Box 70)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, New York, N.Y., 1975-1992, undated (Box 70)
      - Xavier Fourcade, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1979-1980, 1989 (Box 70)
    - North Carolina (Box 70)
      - Asheville Art Center, Asheville, N.C., 1975-1976 (Box 70)
      - Chapel Hill, N.C., Miscellaneous, 1967-1985, n.d (Box 70)
      - Charlotte, N.C. Miscellaneous, 1969, 1971-1974, 1980-1985, undated (Box 70)
      - Duke University, Durham, N.C./Durham, N.C., Miscellaneous, 1967-1972, undated (Box 70)
      - Fayetteville Museum of Art, Fayetteville, N.C., 1981 (Box 70)
      - Greensboro, N.C. Miscellaneous, 1967, 1978 (Box 70)
      - Miscellaneous, 1969-1974, undated (Box 70)
      - North Carolina Museum of Art, Raleigh, N.C., 1969-1989, undated (Box 70)
      - North Carolina State University, Raleigh, N.C., 1968, n.d (Box 70)
      - Raleigh, N.C., Miscellaneous, 1969-1991, undated (Box 70)
      - SECCA (Southeastern Center for Contemporary Art), Winston-Salem, N. C., 1981-1984 (Box 70)
      - Stowe Gallery, Davidson College, 1972, 1974 (Box 70)
      - Weatherspoon Art Gallery, University of North Carolina at Greensboro, N. C., 1973-1976, 1983, undated (Box 70)
      - Western Carolina University, Cullowhee, N. C., 1984 (Box 70)
    - North Dakota, Miscellaneous, 1976, 1984-1985, undated (Box 70)
    - Ohio (Box 70)
      - Akron Art Museum, Akron, Ohio, 1972-1985, undated (Box 70)
      - Allen Memorial Art Museum, Oberlin College, Oberlin, Ohio, 1970-1985, undated (Box 70)
      - Canton Art Institute, Canton, Ohio, 1975-1976 (Box 70)
      - Carl Solway Gallery, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1970-1974, 1980-1982, undated (Box 70)
      - Cincinnati Ohio Miscellaneous, 1963-1984, undated (Box 71)
      - Cleveland Museum of Art, Cleveland, Ohio, 1975-1991, undated (Box 71)
      - Columbus Art Museum, Columbus, Ohio/Columbus College of Art and Design, Columbus, Ohio, 1975-1986, undated (Box 71)
      - Dayton Art Institute, Dayton, Ohio, 1978 (Box 71)
      - Ohio State University, Columbus, Ohio/Public Library of Columbus, Ohio, 1976 (Box 71)
      - Owens Corning Fiberglass, Toledo, Ohio, 1976-1980, n.d (Box 71)
      - Prudential Insurance Company of America, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1983 (Box 71)
      - Toledo, Ohio, Miscellaneous, 1972-1982, 1985-1986, undated (Box 71)
    - Oklahoma, Philbrook Art Center, Tulsa, Okla., Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box 71)
    - Oregon, Portland Art Museum, Portland, Ore., 1975 (Box 71)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 71)
      - Edinboro University of Pennsylvania, Edinboro, Pa., 1991 (Box 71)
      - The Gallery, York, Pa., 1983 (Box 71)
      - Pennsylvania State University, University Park, Pa., 1975-1977 (Box 71)
      - Philadelphia, Pa., Miscellaneous, 1969-1992, undated (Box 71)
      - Pittsburgh, Pa., Miscellaneous, 1980, 1985 (Box 71)
      - Temple University, Elkins Park, Pa., 1984 (Box 71)
    - Rhode Island, Miscellaneous, 1973-1986, undated (Box 71)
    - South Carolina (Box 71)
      - Gibbes Art Gallery, Charleston, S.C., 1979-1981 (Box 71)
      - Greenville County Museum of Art, Greenville, S.C., 1971-1976 (Box 71)
    - Tennessee, Miscellaneous, 1973-1979, 1985-1986, undated (Box 71)
    - Texas (Box 71)
      - Dallas, Tex., Miscellaneous, 1974-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Duane Jarvis, JRJ Architects, Dallas, Tex., 1984 (Box 71)
      - Houston, Tex., Miscellaneous, 1971-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 71)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1985, 1992, undated (Box 71)
    - Utah (Box 71)
      - Harris Fine Arts Center, Brigham Young University, Provo, Utah, 1975-1977, undated (Box 71)
      - Utah Museum of Fine Arts, University of Utah, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1972-1984, undated (Box 71)
    - Vermont (Box 71)
      - Johnson Gallery of Middlebury College, Middlebury, Vt., 1974 (Box 71)
      - Southern Vermont Art Center, Manchester, Vt., 1993-1995 (Box 71)
    - Virginia (Box 72)
      - Edan, Inc., Alexandria, Va., (Landscape Architects), 1984 (Box 72)
      - Federal Reserve Bank of Richmond, Richmond, Va., 1977-1982, 1987, undated (Box 72)
      - The Greater Reston Art Center, Reston, Va., 1978, 1984 (Box 72)
      - Interspace Incorporated, Arlington, VA., 1983 (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous, 1978-1987, 1990-1992, undated (Box 72)
      - Reynolds/Minor Gallery Richmond, Va., 1980-1987, 1990-1991, undated (Box 72)
      - Roanoke Fine Arts Center, Roanoke, Va., 1967, 1969-1972, 1977-1978, undated (Box 72)
      - Thomas Bayly Memorial Building, University of Virginia, Charlottesville, Va., 1975-1985 (Box 72)
      - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, Richmond, Va. (See also OV 114), 1973-1981, 1987, undated (Box 72)
    - Washington (Box 72)
      - Safeco, Corporate Art Collection, Seattle, Wash., 1994 (Box 72)
      - Seattle, Miscellaneous, 1964, 1966, 1976, 1979, 1985 (Box 72)
      - Western Washington State College, Bellingham, Wash., 1975 (Box 72)
    - West Virginia, Charleston Art Gallery, Charleston, W.Va., (Traute Ishida), 1978 (Box 72)
    - Wisconsin (Box 72)
      - John Michael Kohler Arts Center, Sheboygan, Wis., 1877-1981, 1983 (Box 72)
      - Madison Art Center, Madison, Wis./Madison Art Board, Madison, Wis., 1981, 1985-1986, undated (Box 72)
      - Milwaukee Art Center, Milwaukee, Wis., 1976-1978, 1982-1989, undated (Box 72)
  - International Museums and Galleries, 1967-1991, undated; 5.2
    - Argentina, American Embassy, Buenos Aires, 1983 (Box 72)
    - Brazil, Miscellaneous, 1978-1981, undated (Box 72)
    - Canada (Box 72)
      - Art Gallery of Ontario, Grange Park, Toronto/Hyatt Toronto, 1975 (Box 72)
      - Art Gallery of Ontario/The National Gallery of Canada/ Dalhousie University Art Gallery, Nova Scotia, 1974-1976, undated (Box 72)
    - Egypt, Cairo, 1984 (Box 72)
    - England (Box 72)
      - Christie's Contemporary Art, London, England, 1973 (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous, 1980-1988, undated (Box 72)
    - Finland, Miscellaneous, 1983, 1985, undated (Box 72)
    - France (Box 72)
      - Miscellaneous, 1972-1985, 1980-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 72)
      - Paris, Galerie Claude Bernard, 1978-1979, 1985-1986, undated (Box 72)
      - Paris, Miscellaneous, 1970, 1975-1991, undated (Box 72)
      - Speiss, Paris, 1967, 1979-1983, undated (Box 72)
    - Germany, Miscellaneous, 1969, 1972, undated (Box 73)
    - Holland, Miscellaneous, 1981-1985, undated (Box 73)
    - Italy (Box 73)
      - Florence, Italy, 1987, undated (Box 73)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985-1989, undated (Box 73)
      - Rome, Miscellaneous, 1981-1987, undated (Box 73)
    - Morocco, Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Portugal, Miscellaneous, 1979-1986, undated (Box 73)
    - Spain, Miscellaneous, 1990, undated (Box 73)
    - Switzerland, Miscellaneous, 1972, 1977-1980, undated (Box 73)
    - Yugoslavia, Miscellaneous, 1980-1982, undated (Box 73)
    - Oversized materials, Museums and Galleries, 1952-2000, undated (Box OV 114)
- Subject Files, 1952, 1960-2001, undated; Series 6; (Box 73-88, OV 115, 116; 15.5 linear feet)
  Numerous files arranged by subject headings established by the gallery that contain information collected and maintained by the gallery on various art medium, artists of interest, exhibition catalogs from museums and other galleries, and information about small and fine art presses. Of particular interest are several folders entitled "Fine Art Printers & Publishers." Barbara Fendrick's early years in the art business centered upon exhibiting, promoting, and selling prints produced by young, emerging American artists. The information found here documents her growing personal relationships with some of the most prominent artists and printmakers of this era.
  The overall arrangement of the series is generally alphabetical by subject heading, except for exhibition catalogs of group shows, which are arranged chronologically by year. Catalogs featuring a single artist are first arranged alphabetically by name of artist, thereafter, chronologically by year. Within individual folders the material is generally arranged chronologically by year.
  Individual artists found listed in this series may also have additional related files in Series 1, Artists Files and Series 4, Exhibition Files.
  - African American Artists, C-W, undated, 1970-1993; (3 folders) (Box 73)
  - African American Artists and Exhibits, 1976-1990, undated (Box 73)
  - American Craft Movement, 1979-circa 1989, undated (Box 73)
  - Animals in Art, 1979-1986, undated (Box 73)
  - Arc International Furniture Catalog, 1987-1981; (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Architectural Ceramics, 1980-1984, undated (Box 73)
  - Architecture, 1977-1987, undated (Box 73)
  - Art and Laws, 1989-1992, undated (Box 73)
  - Art Society of the International Monetary Fund, 1962-1966, undated (Box 73)
  - Artists' Cards (Box 73)
    - Asher, Lila Oliver, undated (Box 73)
    - Bart, Harriet, 1991 (Box 73)
    - Baskins, Leonard and Gehenna Press (from Delphic Arts), undated (Box 73)
    - Childs, Bernard, 1967-1969 (Box 73)
    - Clark, Howard and Kathryn, 1980-1981 (Box 73)
    - Davis, Gene, 1969 (Box 73)
    - Debutler, Jacqueline, undated (Box 73)
    - Demarais, Joe, 1967 (Box 73)
    - Franklin, Herbert and Barbara, 1965, undated (Box 73)
    - Freed, Ernest, 1963-1968 (Box 73)
    - Grashow, James (from Pratt Graphic Arts Center, special edition), undated (Box 73)
    - Hahn, Judy and Jon (Box 73)
    - Jacometti, Nesto, editor (works from Éditions L'Œuvre de Gravée), 1962-1967, undated (Box 73)
    - Jéan, Ponce de (See also Fendrick Folios, Ltd.), 1969, 1971, undated (Box 73)
    - Landier, Henri (from La Galerie "le Novel Essor"), 1964 (Box 73)
    - Levy Family, undated (Box 73)
    - Malone, Robert R., 1967 (Box 73)
    - Margo, Boris, 1970 (Box 73)
    - Pastan, Linda, 1979, undated (Box 73)
    - Phillips, Matt, undated (Box 73)
    - Romano, Clare and John Ross, 1967- undated (Box 73)
    - Smith, R.A., 1966 (Box 73)
    - Stevenson, Brockie, undated (Box 73)
    - Unidentified woodblock, undated (Box 73)
  - Artists of Interest, 1986-1993, undated; (5 folders) (Box 74)
  - Arts and Crafts, 1974-1981, undated (Box 74)
  - Audio Visual Tapes on Art Topics (2 shoe boxes), 1995, undated (Box 74)
  - Book Art (Box 74)
    - Artists, A-C, 1968-1993, undated; (3 folders) (Box 74)
    - Artists, D-W, 1968-1993, undated; (4 folders) (Box 75)
    - General, 1967-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 75)
    - Unpublished Manuscript by Daniel Fendrick, with Research Materials, and Notes, 1958, 1965- 1983, undated; (9 folders) (Box 75)
  - Cars in Art, 1976-1977, undated (Box 76)
  - Catalogs (Gallery and Museum), 1965-1985; (17 folders; see also OV 115) (Box 76)
  - Catalogs (Gallery and Museum), 1986-1991, undated; (8 folders) (Box 77)
  - Catalogs (Individual Artists), A-S, 1967-1999; (10 folders; see also OV 116) (Box 77)
  - Catalogs (Individual Artists), T-W, 1983-1989; (2 folders; see also OV 116) (Box 78)
  - Clay Artists, A-Z, 1973-1984, undated; (6 folders) (Box 78)
  - Clay Artists, Groups Shows, 1976-1981, undated (Box 78)
  - Collage, 1978, 1983, undated (Box 78)
  - Collectors Compendium, undated (Box 78)
  - Conservators, 1992, undated (Box 78)
  - Corporate Art, 1986-1989, undated (Box 78)
  - Design (Box 78)
  - Dolls, 1980-1981, undated (Box 78)
  - Drawings of Interest, 1975-1980 (Box 78)
  - Ethan Bogen/Carnegie Corporation, 1988-1991, undated (Box 78)
  - Exhibit Announcements, Miscellaneous, 1973-2001, undated (Box 78)
  - Experimental Photography, 1988-1990, undated (Box 78)
  - Fendrick, Daniel, "The American Print Market in the Sixties,", 1966 (Box 78)
  - Fendrick Folios, Ltd., 1967-1971, undated; (3 folders; see also, same series, Artists' Cards) (Box 79)
  - Fendrick Gallery "Art Meets Object" Editions, 1967-1970, undated (Box 79)
  - Films and Lectures, 1973-1974, undated (Box 79)
  - Fine Art Printers & Publishers (Box 79)
    - Antarès, ?ditions d'Art, Saint-Cloud, France, 1963-1969 (Box 79)
    - Arion Press, San Francisco, Calif., 1975-1976, 1993, undated (Box 79)
    - Associated American Artists, New York, N.Y., 1984-1988, undated; (2 folders) (Box 79)
    - Berggruen & Cie., Paris, France, 1963-1965 (Box 79)
    - Brooke Alexander, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1977-1991, undated; (3 folders) (Box 79)
    - Castelli Graphics, New York, N.Y., 1985-1989 (Box 79)
    - Crown Point Press, San Francisco, Calif. and New York, N.Y., 1986-1990 (Box 79)
    - Donn H. Steward, Halesite, N.Y., 1974-1985, undated (Box 79)
    - Fia, Inc., Kyoto, Japan, 1990-1991, undated (Box 79)
    - Gemini G.E.L., Los Angeles, Calif., 1967-1996, undated; (3 folders) (Box 79)
    - Lincoln Center/List Art Poster and Print Program, New York, N.Y., 1989-2000 (Box 80)
    - Miscellaneous Printers/Publishers, A-X, 1961-1996, undated; (6 folders) (Box 80)
    - Multiples, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1967, 1971-1989, undated; (5 folders) (Box 80)
    - Nicolas Rauch, S.A., Geneva, Switzerland, 1962-1965 (Box 80)
    - Notes and Miscellaneous Material, 1989, 1991, undated (Box 80)
    - Pace Editions, Inc., New York, N.Y., 1969-1991, undated; (4 folders) (Box 81)
    - Petersburg Press, London, England, 1967-1991, undated; (9 folders) (Box 81)
    - Rutgers Archives for Printmaking Studios, New Brunswick, N.J., 1992 (Box 81)
    - Tamarind Institute (formerly Tamarind Lithography Workshop), Albuquerque, N. Mex., 1960-1995, undated (Box 81)
    - Tamarind Institute (formerly Tamarind Lithography Workshop), Albuquerque, N. Mex., 1960-1995, undated; (2 folders) (Box 81)
    - Tandem Press, Madison, Wis., 1990-1995 (Box 81)
    - Tyler Graphics, Ltd., Mt. Kisco, N.Y., 1974-1995, undated; (7 folders) (Box 81)
    - Tyler Graphics, Ltd., Mt. Kisco, N.Y., 1974-1995, undated; (6 folders) (Box 82)
    - Universal Limited Art Editions (U.L.A.E.), West Islip, N.Y., 1964-1983; (13 folders) (Box 82)
    - Universal Limited Art Editions (U.L.A.E.), West Islip, N.Y., 1984-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 83)
    - Vermillion Editions, Ltd., Minneapolis, Minn., circa 1981-1992 (Box 83)
  - First International Water Sculpture Competition, 1982-1984, undated; (6 folders) (Box 83)
  - Five Finger Formation Art Game, 1973 (Box 83)
  - Folk Art, 1974-2001, undated; (3 folders) (Box 83)
  - Folk Artists, A-P, 1964-1986, undated; (3 folders) (Box 83)
  - Folk Artists, S-W, 1964-1986, undated (Box 83)
  - Folk Artists, Santa Fe, NM, 1975-1986, undated; (2 folders) (Box 83)
  - Furniture Artists, A-S, 1981-1991, undated; (5 folders) (Box 84)
  - Furniture as Art, 1979-1994, undated; (3 folders) (Box 84)
  - Glass, Czech, 1980-1983, undated; (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Glass Art, 1980-1998, undated (Box 84)
  - Glass Artists, B-V, 1973-1985, undated; (4 folders) (Box 84)
  - Handmade Paper, 1975-1993, undated; (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Ideas for Future Shows, 1990-1991, undated Ironwork, 1981-1982, undated (Box 84)
  - Items of Interest, 1988-1992, undated; (2 folders) (Box 84)
  - Japanese Possibilities, 1987-1991, undated; (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - Jewelry, 1972-1987, undated (Box 85)
  - Landscape Architects, 1983-1986, undated (Box 85)
  - Landscape Art, 1977, 1981-1984 (Box 85)
  - Mayer, Mrs. R. L., 1963-1967, undated (Box 85)
  - Miscellaneous Articles About Art-Related Topics, 1972-1999, undated (Box 85)
  - Mitsui, Masako, 1974-1990, undated; (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - Naive Art, circa, 1985 (Box 85)
  - National Endowment for the Arts Artist Exchange Fellowships, 985, undated (Box 85)
  - Native American Fine Arts, Crafts, and Antiques, 1972-1984, undated; (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - "New, Fun & Funk" Artists, B-S, 1974-1980, undated; (2 folders) (Box 85)
  - "New Realists,", 1965-1984, undated (Box 85)
  - New York Information, 1998-2000, undated (Box 85)
  - Notes Regarding Esmarian/Ozawa, 1990, undated (Box 85)
  - Painters of Interest, A - R, 1977-1983, undated; (3 folders) (Box 85)
  - Painters of Interest, S - W, 1966-1981, undated; (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Painting, 1978-1981, undated (Box 86)
  - Paper Collages, 1978-1984, undated; (2 folders) (Box 86)
  - Personal Photographs of Barbara Fendrick and Family, 1976, 1978 (Box 86)
  - Photography, 1972-1988, undated; (4 folders) (Box 86)